{
    "id": "6c7e87eabe51405d892061bf683834b9",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I enjoy watching movies ………………………. the cinema.",
            "description": "At is used to indicate position at a point. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided to quit his job …………………………. several reasons.",
            "description": "For + reasons",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I like walking …………………………. the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting started exactly ……………………… time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You look pretty ……………………… this photo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the end, she decided to marry her childhood friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "At",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie is not very interesting ………………………….. the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You never see things ………………………….. my point of view.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "in",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It will take longer if you go ……………………………. boat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your dad …………………………… the phone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you angry ………………………… him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She belongs ………………………… a literary club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}